Yeah.
Is there anything more you can tell me about the road to Meridian?
Sunk in Nevada has devoted considerable resources to making it safe.
But by the sun's witnesses being harder to control in peace than it was during the war, machines grow more dangerous all the time.
And to that, bandits and new reports of this corruption was stretched in to protect a few outposts like this one.
That's for everywhere else.
Well traveling your own risk
the world beyond the sacred land I need to find Olen and learn everything.
He knows who the killers were, How they saw me through his focus Her The woman is one who looks like me.
Why they want me dead.
Poland's trail leads to Meridian.
When I catch him, he will talk
and he will pay for all the lives he's ruined.
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah
Okay.
Uh huh
Oh, mhm.
Pissing around and show yourself
Yeah,
come out I'll make it quick
If you won't fight, Why don't you run on home?
Show your face so I could slice it off
Yeah,
yeah
Die away
My life is on the line to e Wanna see the sun rise again
Oh,
got you located
E
right here.
You shut off.
Yeah,
yeah,
Yes.
Yeah.
God.
Okay,
Disappeared.
I won't quit till I find you.
Okay?
Yeah.
Story said patients.
Mhm.
Yeah.
You know,
No
can stop tensing up.
Yeah.
Uh huh.
Has
Yeah,
we will.
yeah.
Well enough.
Right.
Thanks for Okay,
but
right.
Okay.
Mhm
first came from Yeah.
Mhm.
Yeah.
Yes,
Right
for
Okay,
right.
You okay?
Yeah.
Yeah,
yeah,
yeah, yeah.
Sweet,
I think.
Mhm.
No.
Oh, uh,
okay.
Thank you.
Oh,
okay.
Yeah.
Should be out there fighting machines.
I'm pacing around here from
the global curse down
shapes.
It's a crime.
I should report it to the sun court.
We believe.
Believe, believe, believe, believe.
Thanks,
e Have nothing for you, I'm afraid.
Okay.
I mean freedom.
Yeah,
We all have our place.
In the order of things.
It lived up to their usual step.
I've seen this four times already.
You?
Oh, wonderful.
Yeah.
Perfect weather for war.
I'm sorry for the wait, but all goods entering the city are subject to search.
This is outrageous.
Where loyal citizens How long do we have to wait?
What am I supposed to do?
Just sit here and let everything spoiled.
I thought Meridian was open.
Toe are Kharja What happened?
Toe?
Ursa has nothing to do with us.
Yeah, I've seen better.
Yeah.
If I don't get my place, the buyer soon, they'll cancel the contract.
What's going on here?
Molins In there somewhere.
And so's errand.
That other Outlander I talked to the night before the proving Aaron said he'd introduce me to a sister if I visited Meridian.
Said she was Captain of the Vanguard.
Just finish your business here and be gone.
Outlander
Cities locked down on account of the murder.
Good luck getting throughout landed.
If this keeps up, I'll be broken a month.
We all have our place in the order of things.
It's always the merchants who suffer.
Okay.
Damn it
told
Don't be.
Stop right there.
In light of the recent attack, no stranger passes into Meridian without submitting to search.
Recent attack.
What are you talking about?
The murder of Captain Ursa and Havan guards, Of course.
Ambushed by Shadow Carter forces in Red Ridge Pass IRSA You mean Erin's sister is dead?
How would you know his name?
I know.
Errand summon him.
I need to speak to him.
Hat.
I doubt that Aaron, the new captain of the vanguard a man in grief, is going to waste his time on a grimy Outlander.
Hey, Loy!
Hey!
You're alive!
I thought you were dead.
Make way!
All the way to Meridian just to see me.
Have you been drinking?
Ah, not really.
A little.
So you're alive.
We should celebrate it.
Drinks on May.
We need to talk alone and you need to pull together over there.
So you approve?
Of course I approve.
From now on, she may come and go from this city as she pleases.
As you wish, sir.
They're alone.
As you asked.
What do you want to tell me?
I heard what happened to IRSA.
I'm sorry.
I know she was special to you.
Special to me?
Yeah.
Special toe, Everyone.
She always knew what to do.
Bust everyone around.
Just kept me in line.
Now I'm supposed toe fill her shoes instead.
Here I am stumbling around in them.
Give yourself some time.
You'll find your footing.
Not at the rate I've been drinking.
And what would your sister have said about that?
I know you're right.
I should expect more of myself.
She always did.
Then stop feeling sorry for yourself and live up to her example.
So much for a shoulder to cry on.
Everybody loses people they care about.
Oh, yeah.
I lost someone too.
At the proving the man who raised me.
His name was roast.
That's terrible.
But why is it every time something terrible happens, everyone else tells you the worst thing that ever happened to them is so that makes it easier.
Yeah.
Why is that?
Anyway, there is something you wanted to tell me.
A lot has happened since we last spoke.
The proving was attacked by a group of killers.
Not many of us survived.
We were in the village when we heard explosions up on the mountain.
Some of your braves came back.
Said most of the contestants were dead.
I've never heard such a wail of grief.
Is the sound that rose up from your people?
How did you survive?
How I survived is less important than how I was targeted.
Targeted?
What do you mean?
The killers came for me because of colon.
But he's a friend.
No, he's a traitor.
I don't know who the killers are or what they want, but I do know that Colin is working with them.
But all right, this'll I don't need you to understand.
Errand.
I just need you to take me to him.
He's not here.
He went scrounging for scrapping relics days ago.
It could be anywhere.
Are there any places he frequents?
Places he returns to ah, house here in Meridian.
Okay, then take me there.
I need to search it.
I guess a za long as I'm there to witness the search.
Okay.
So many people here, all talking at once.
How does anyone think I don't?
I just drink.
I've got all the years that girl is she and more.
Apparently they're letting anyone into the city these days.
Find you?
Yeah.
How long will have died in his palace till they siege to the Citadel.
Does he lack the stomach for justice?
Blood for blood, Vengeance for Ursa year after year.
Why does he spare those who enslaved and tortured and butchered errant?
You should want vengeance more than anyone your own sister murdered and her death unavenged.
One more word you scorched out slag.
I'll throw you in jail myself.
Get out of here.
Where I'll give you all the kick in the ass.
What did he mean about ercis murder?
Not now.
Yeah?
Yeah.
Okay.
How are we going to get in?
Oh, Oh, that was subtle.
Here we are trying to break anything that other than the door.
All of this for one man.
It pays to have connections in the Sun Kings court.
Does he know the Sun King personally?
No.
Hay served the court as a scout sometimes and sold ancient trinkets to nobles.
But he never had an audience with the King.
If you're right and Olin's into something dark Sun, King of Odd has nothing to do with it.
I'd stake my life on that.
Did Ola never invite you in?
Yeah.
Closest I got was a doorstep toe.
Help him home after a night out.
We drank a river that night, but I hold it well, usually.
Are you sure you're OK?
I'm sober enough.
All right?
I don't need another lecture.
That's not what I meant.
I was talking about what happened outside with the crowd.
I don't wanna talk about that.
We're here because of what you said about Oland.
So do what you need to do
is
yeah.
A corner of this road is frayed on the floor near it is warned.
Let's see what's underneath.
Yeah.
Hey, how did that get here?
Question is how to get through it without a key.
You won't.
That's evolved.
Hatch of a Zara make.
Nothing gets through.
We'll see about that.
Call it a day, girl.
You're wasting time.
Yeah.
Looks big and heavy.
Could do a lot of damage if it fell down.
Let's give it a little push.
Right.
Uh, you know, things like that.
Yeah.
I did say not to break anything, didn't I?
To me
beat It looks like a picture of Owen's family
from you.
Time to get to the bottom of this.
Looks like Olin kept a journal.
Olin.
I knew he could read contracts, but I never took him for a poet, No doubt.
Now, Olin knew I was targeted.
A map.
The glitch show places he visited
serve and they live.
Disobey.
And I will open their throats and leave their corpses to prune in the sun.
They took his wife and child captive.
They?
Who's they?
The killers.
They told him to obey or they kill his family.
There's your proof.
Read the last page.
He writes about meeting me in the order to kill me.
He called himself a friend.
That backstabbing cheat.
How did you learn to read cliffs and these things that you see?
How do you do it?
The focus.
It reveals the unseen and Olin's focus.
It's the same.
The device is the same.
But somehow Olen and the killers can speak to each other with their focus is over distances and see through each other's focuses, too.
Like looking through each other's eyes.
So that's how the killers saw you through Olin.
Yes.
So far as I could tell.
Now that I know where to find Dolan, I should be on my way all by yourself.
Leave it to me.
I'm faster on my own.
Wait.
If that device lets you see the unseen out of the way errand.
I'm asking you to help me.
A lawyer.
I need to know who killed IRSA.
Not just that, the Shadow Kharja Army.
I know that, but the exact soldiers who did it I'm sorry about your sister, but that's your war, not mine.
Don't act like this isn't personal.
You came here hunting the people who nearly killed you.
Who massacred your people?
Why should you have justice and not me?
Look, I'll head for Red Rich Pass where Irs's body was found and wait for you there.
A few minutes of your focus is all I need.
Don't make me beg Red Ridge past.
You said
I'll see what I can.
Dio
Yes.
Wait
ST you can
won't thats place.
It's an Oscar.
I would argue like nothing I've ever smelled before.
Is that some kind of spice?
Hm?
You're now Lander Nora.
From the look of you.
I bet your machine hunter too.
I've hunted my share.
I'm known as a skilled hunter back home in Bonheur.
So I thought I'd try my luck at the lodge.
I thought I'd be simple Hunt machines gain ranks, see who's best.
But it doesn't work like that at all.
It's all rigged to keep the card at the head of the line.
If you're not Kharja, you'll never rise in the ranks.
When Sun king of Odd took over, he promised the new day Meridian open toe all.
But it's a sham.
Sure you could get a seat of the feast, But you just can't eat the food.
Sounds like someone needs to shake things up with the lodge.
Maybe, but it isn't gonna be me.
I don't need those snobs to tell me I can hunt going home.
If you decide to go, Be sure to give them a good old fashioned Bennack.
Farewell, Mark in my honor, ba Nuke.
Farewell, Mark.
What's that?
Piss on the floor?
Preferably someplace they won't find it until it gets nice and sour.
The people here won't stand for hearing we're doing has proven itself above such things.
Only the finest kids here speak.
Don't have.
Yeah,
Meridian is a month
Stood from General find Group for a fair price.
Shoots of bandits trying to get past me.
I love a fight.
These aren't good.
Yeah,
right.
Date,
check out these wares.
See this?
These aren't the necessities way
Sure is better.
Don't pass up these
the nor will serve.
They always do.
It's that barbarian resilience
I hate
I have found So
I hope the ceasefire weeks to
these aren't goods.
Their necessities
don't pass up These good
You need to win three half sons that are hunting grounds to gain admittance to the lodge.
You mean these Very well then.
Congratulations and welcome.
Our members reap rewards and adventure and live on in legend.
And I remember now.
No, you're only a fledgling junior members air called thrushes to join and become a thrush, you need a senior member called a hawk to sponsor you.
So I need to find a hawk.
Yes, but ah Hawk can only sponsor one hunter at a time.
I'm afraid most of them already have one.
I have overcome or sods.
Where do I start?
Upstairs.
Present yourself to the Sun Hawk.
A cease Our leader who should introduce you to Ah hawk.
I hope it's worth it.
What do you mean?
You'll see?
Yeah.
Mhm.
Yeah,
By the sun.
King of Odds Edict really is taking effect.
I never thought I'd see a Nora here And a woman at that.
What edict?
King of Odd insisted that the Hunter's lodge had toe.
Welcome everyone Man!
Woman Outlander, Regardless of tribe.
Ursa, Captain of the vanguard came in and delivered that news personally.
You should have been there.
It was glorious, but I figured they would sweep it under the rug and say no woman or Outlander qualified.
Yet here you are.
Are you remember me?
No.
Kharja don't exactly encourage their daughters to run around hunting machines.
But all the changes in Meridian have been good to me.
So you have marks for me.
What do you mean?
From the hunting grounds?
Oh, right.
You're new here.
What do you want with my marks?
You hunters and your badges?
I'm not gonna take them.
I'm going to give you a weapon that sets you apart.
What do I do with these marks?
If you earn marks in all three trials at each of the five hunting grounds come to me.
I can give you up to three weapons.
One for 15 half sons, one for 15 full sons and one you'll love for all blazing suns.
I need a few more.
Okay.
Once you get marks from the trials at every hunting ground, come back and we'll see what I can give you.
That's mhm.
What have we here?
Anura fledge.
But I've been hunting longer than you have.
Are you a fledgling?
Not for long.
I have a hawk who's about to sponsor me.
So you're out of luck.
Typical savage barging in here without a thought right after one of her own was killed.
Go away, Thio.
Mhm.
Yeah, Yeah.
I've been trophy hunting for years.
Still haven't gotten a sponsor.
Mhm.
I'd asked Alana to sponsor me, but her sponsor just died.
Can't imagine what she must be going through.
Yeah.
Just excuse us.
The machine writer graces us with her presence.
You're a Nora, Are you not a fighter from the savage lands, the sacred land.
But yes, I thought for everything I got.
Uh huh.
Tell me, Do the Nora often wonder into other people's homes and do whatever they like?
Of course not.
But that is what you're doing right now.
Stinking up our lodge, pestering your betters.
You're hardly my better.
Legan said I had to meet you to become a member.
That would be true if there were any chance of you becoming a member.
But you're a savage and no savage will rise in the ranks of the Hunters Lodge while I am the son Hawk now begun.
No, I was led to believe there are rules here.
If they count for nothing than even your position is meaningless.
So quit blustering and tell me, Is there a hawk who is free to sponsor me?
Very well.
Helena is free.
Wouldn't that be fitting trash sponsoring trash?
Now get out of my sight.
Mhm
Here to Alana.
Asi said You were a hawk without a fledgling to sponsor.
Or are you trying to drive me off, too?
It's okay.
I've dealt with worse.
Mhm.
I'll bet you have.
But you're wrong.
It's not okay, Especially not today.
What happened today?
One of our own just died fighting Red Ma.
You'll never face a more dangerous thunder jock cuts through trees, rocks, people.
I'm sorry to hear that it's part of the hunt.
Is there any actual hunting in this lodge?
So far, it's been all talk.
Yes, of course.
You fight a machine, then bring its trophy to a cease the Sun Hawk that no one could deny.
You brought it down a cease.
What's his story?
He's the son Hawk of the lodge, the highest ranking assholes.
Sorry, remember, he's taken down ravages stalkers, behemoths.
So I've taken down a lot of machines, as if I even brought down to storm birds.
But he's a Hawk who brought into trophies first.
That's how it works.
Whichever hog defeats the greatest machine first becomes the son Hawk.
Who is this llegan?
The man at the door llegan.
He's a hawk.
He had an impressive run in his day, but he doesn't fight anymore.
He supports the lodge in other ways, unlike the other Hawks who hoard all of us, kills and drink the bar dry.
How does one become a hawk when a hawk dies, his thrushes promoted in his place.
No matter how anyone feels about it, I'm ready to hunt.
So tell me, what do I have to dio?
You want them to regret looking down on you, Then speak to them in their language.
Kill three saw tubes to ravages and a stalker deliver their trophies directly to a cease that should shut them all up.
So if I do that, you'll sponsor me.
I'll consider it just to make a C spoil.
So,
um,
the record of red Mumbai enquiring Jan minimum historian and residents at the Hunter's Lodge.
It is well known that fax recede into fictions as they become memories and fresh fax themselves are ephemeral.
Among the rumors and Legends of the South.
This is especially true in the case of Red Ma, the most terrible of thunder jaws, a machine which is nothing if not legendary.
Few who have laid eyes opponent have survived, and among them even fewer can be trusted not to embellish their tails.
All that said here, I have endeavored to truthfully chronicle all the calamities attributed to the beast and all the expeditions meant to end such calamities once and for all.
None have succeeded.
As of this writing, the terror of the South still roams free.
Scarred, perhaps, but deadly is the day the sun first shone upon its armored hide.
In the early spring of the 18th year of the Reign of the Sun King Geron, a freehold, was destroyed near the hands of the flood.
Nine bodies were recovered, ate riddled with cannon rounds.
One flattened completely.
No witnesses survived, though never proven.
This is widely thought to be read Mas First attack In the late spring of the 18th year of the Reign of the Sun King Giron, an expedition of four hunters set out from Sunstone Rock to track the machine or machines responsible for the destruction of the freehold.
None returned.
Their bodies were subsequently found in the south.
Three blasted, one stomped, Never proven but thought to be read mas work.
In the early summer of the 18th year of the Reign of the Sun King Giron, an expedition of six mercenaries set out from Meridian to attract the machine or machines responsible for the loss is described above.
One returned rips crushed, clavicle fractured.
He spoke of a thunder jaw, which split a man in half with a single bite.
This is the first confirmed sighting of the legendary machine and the one which gave it a name.
In the late summer of the 18th year of the reign of the Sun King Giron, an expedition of eight set off from Meridian to track Red Ma.
None returned.
Six bodies were found near black wing snag.
One blasted three, stomped to eviscerated.
One swallowed his own tongue, evidently in a spasm of terror, suffocating in the autumn of the 18th year of his reign, the Sun King Giron commanded the Hunter's lodge to send an expedition south in pursuit of Red Ma.
After numerous logistical delays, three hawks and their thrushes set out in winter Onley.
One pair returned, reporting the deaths of the others to blasted.
One stomped, one decapitated.
The survivors were sacrificed for cowardice, one gutted by a sawtooth, the others cured by Kestral.
After this setback, members of the lodge grew wary of pursuing the legendary Thunder Jaw Onley.
The proudest hawks even considered it Asper.
Ants to the lodge, however foolish in their ambition, eagerly took part in subsequent hunts.
In the summer of the 19th year of the Reign of the Sun King Geron, the destruction of a caravan south of the Spur, Flint's three blasted to stomped.
One immolated reignited interest in Red Ma.
Three expeditions totaling 15 mercenaries went after the machine with only three survivors.
Nine blasted, three stomped to eviscerated one liquefied.
In the early spring of the 20th year of the Reign of the Sun King Geron, a cohort of 12 soldiers headed from the rain, gathers to the A light were set upon by the beast Onley.
One survived, one blasted, one stomped, 10 crushed when they're fleeing, Footsteps triggered an avalanche in the late spring of the 20th year of the reign of the Sun King Giron.
Three cohorts totaling 34 men went in search of bread.
Ma.
Alas, they were ambushed by stalkers, and only four survived.
24th Night six exploded, understandably descended Pursuit of Red Mall For some time in the summer of the first year of the reign of the Sun King VOD, a group of six saucer and traders were attacked by the beast.
One blasted, three stomped one spit into a ravine.
The lone Survivor petition captain nurses to send the vanguard after the monster, but the request was denied.
However, three additional expeditions comprised of mercenaries and hunters aspiring to the lodge, were subsequently commissioned.
Autumn.
Seven men to blasted, three stomped, one tripped on his own spear.
One survivor winter.
Nine men, three blasted to stomped to died from frostbite.
Two survivors spring.
11 men, five blasted, one stopped.
Three retreated off a cliff to survivors.
Last known sighting of red Ma occurred in the spring of the third year of the Reign of the Sun King of odd tar Cas.
Hawk of the Lodge got word of a sighting near Thunderhead and set off to take the beast on his own.
His thrush tell Lana arrived at the scene.
Too late.
Justice targets was dying of his wounds.
Multiple preparations.
Talon a testified that has read more lumbered off through the trees.
She could see the spear of her mentor embedded in its hide.
No doubt now Olin knew I was targeted
Fourth day I am a traitor now and see no way out If I start at the beginning how they turned me Perhaps I can see something I missed.
No, there is no escape.
What good can writing it dio 10th day you gave me this folio when you taught me to write All these years later it still smells of you Lavender and ash of the forge All I have left of you write me notes You said when you gave it share your thoughts Tear the leaves Send the pages to show I'm thinking of you but I never did Hands to grubby to touch parchment How I wish I had done is you said how I wish I could Now 15th day the same dream Your hair in the forge light our sons weight on my shoulders All of us free You turn to me and whisper It is a dream I answer Yes, I know and then wake alone.
Even awake my life as a dream.
A life.
My treachery will not buy your freedom.
It only buys time.
But every moment you live that he lives.
If treachery is the cost, I will pant 34th day every week the device calls me in secret to a new dig.
We work like men with whips to our backs as though it was left to us to upturn the soil of the entire earth.
And time has run low scrabbling to find the carcasses of ancient demons.
It's the weapons they want must be What misery am I helping birth into this land?
38th day I drink with Aaron and Ursa, but not even the sweetest Brooke and wash the taste of guilt from my mouth.
Every day my silence betrays them.
Villains watched through the device.
I keep expecting Ursa to stick a blade through my throat but fire and spent.
She does not suspect me a better liar than I thought.
Myself must be 54th day fitful sleep the past three nights thinking on that nor a girl.
Why did it order her killed?
The device must be even so What threat could she pose way heard explosions and distant screams from the village.
I thought the savages might blame us.
Turn on us.
I almost wished for it, but they're matriarchs.
Ordered us Khan.
We fled to the border with an escort of braves crossed update Our now I am called to a dig in the rock res.
They promise another glimpse of you of our son.
How I hope to see you both.
You know
I'm